<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://makabakalalala.github.io</id>
    <title>Da Chen Group</title>
    <updated>2021-12-27T07:32:36.965Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://makabakalalala.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://makabakalalala.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>&lt;html&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot;&gt;Welcome to join us&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;</subtitle>
    <logo>https://makabakalalala.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://makabakalalala.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Da Chen Group</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publications]]></title>
        <id>https://makabakalalala.github.io/post/di-san-pian-wen-zhang</id>
        <link href="https://makabakalalala.github.io/post/di-san-pian-wen-zhang">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-12-16T13:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><font size=6><strong>Geodesic Paths for Image Segmentation With Implicit Region-Based Homogeneity Enhancement</strong></font><br>
<font size=6>Source publications: IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON IMAGE PROCESSING<br>
DOI: 10.1109/TIP.2021.3078106<br>
Abstract:<br>
Minimal paths are regarded as a powerful and efficient tool for boundary detection and image segmentation due to its global optimality and the well-established numerical solutions such as fast marching method. In this paper, we introduce a flexible interactive image segmentation model based on the Eikonal partial differential equation (PDE) framework in conjunction with region-based homogeneity enhancement. A key ingredient in the introduced model is the construction of local geodesic metrics, which are capable of  integrating anisotropic and asymmetric edge features, implicit region-based homogeneity features and/or curvature regularization. The incorporation of the region-based homogeneity features into the metrics considered relies on an implicit representation of these features, which is one of the contributions of this work. Moreover, we also introduce a way to build simple closed contours as the concatenation of two disjoint open curves.Experimental results prove that the proposed model indeed outperforms state-of-the-art minimal paths-based image segmentation approaches.</font></p>
<hr/>
<font size=6><strong>A Generalized Asymmetric Dual-Front Model for Active Contours and Image Segmentation</strong></font>
<p><font size=6>Source publications: IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON IMAGE PROCESSING</p>
<p>DOI: 10.1109/TIP.2021.3078102<br>
Abstract:<br>
The Voronoi diagram-based dual-front scheme is known as a powerful and efficient technique for addressing the image segmentation and domain partitioning problems. In the basic formulation of existing dual-front approaches, the evolving contour can be considered as the interfaces of adjacent Voronoi regions. Among these dual-front models, a crucial ingredient is regarded as the geodesic metrics by which the geodesic distances and the corresponding Voronoi diagram can be estimated. In this paper, we introduce a new dual-front model based on asymmetric quadratic metrics. These metrics considered are built by the integration of the image features and a vector field derived from the evolving contour. The use of the asymmetry enhancement can reduce the risk for the segmentation contours being stuck at false positions, especially when the initial curves are far away from the target boundaries or the images have complicated intensity distributions. Moreover, the proposed dual-front model can be applied for image segmentation in conjunction with various region-based homogeneity terms. The numerical experiments on both synthetic and real images show that the proposed dual-front model indeed achieves encouraging results.</font></p>
<hr/>
<font size=6><strong>Anisotropic tubular minimal path model with fast marching front freezing scheme</strong></font>
<p><font size=6>Source publications: PATTERN RECOGNITION</p>
<p>DOI: :10.1016/j.patcog.2020.107349<br>
Abstract:<br>
In this work, we introduce an anisotropic minimal path model based on a new Riemannian tensor integrating the crossing-adaptive anisotropic radius-lifted tensor field and the front freezing indicator by appearance and path features. The non-local path feature only can be obtained during the geodesic distance computation process by the fast marching method. The predefined criterion derived from path feature is able to steer the front evolution by freezing the point causing high bending of the geodesic to solve the shortcut problem. We performed qualitative and quantitative experiments on synthetic and real images (including retinal vessels, rivers and roads) and compare<br>
with the minimal path models with classical anisotropic Riemannian metric and dynamic isotropic metric, which demonstrated the proposed method can detect desired targets from complex tubular tree structures. (C) 2020 Elsevier Ltd. All rights reserved.</font></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>